Now everybody lift your hands up!
Sing about what you are dreaming!
Always stand up!
Raise up the flag that can't be beaten!
Gotta keep up!
We'll get past every wall that's
in our wake, go without hesitation!
Hands up!
We just have to press on a little more.
To get to the answers we're looking for.
We came to this new world
believing that surely someday.
We just might find the way.
All the pieces of our dreams
have now come together.
Our bonds won't waver.
With our dreaming hand.
Let's head on towards.
A bright new future.
Now everybody lift your hands up.
Sing about what you are dreaming.
Always stand up.
Raise up the flag that you believe in.
Gotta keep up.
We'll get past everyone that's in our way.
Let's head on never stopping.
Only look up.
Keep your head up way up high.
Always step up.
If waves are rough, jump to the sky.
Never give up.
Our wishes, they will come together.
And lead us on for the future.
We drift on riding the waves.
Towards another shore day by day.
There are many meetings, many goodbyes.
Underneath the flag we fly.
I'll remember the pain within.
I'll keep it in my heart forever.
And never take it lightly.
But I won't surrender.
This freedom I will keep in mind.
I'll keep holding on, never stop it.
Now everybody lift your hands up.
Sing about what you are dreaming.
Always stand up.
Raise up the flag that you believe in.
Gotta keep up.
We'll get past everyone that's in our way.
Let's head on, never stop it.
Only look up, keep your
head up, way up high.
Always step up, if brains
are rough, jump to the sky.
Never give up, our wishes,
they will come together.
And lead us on for the future.
Hands up.
listen white hunter i'm telling you
right now keep your distance from caesar.
last thing i need to deal with is us
taking turns squeezing each other's hearts.
i know you're filled
with hellfire right now
but save it until i get
my heart back from vergo.
as long as we're on this island
you're following my orders got it.
I took the shortest route here.
And I was moving as fast as I could.
Where are you? Vergo!
Damn it, you're incessantly irritating.
I got you.
Spoke too soon there.
Unflammable type.
Me, I'll gasp!
What's your problem?
What reason do you have for attacking me?
Other than you trying to kill me
and my friends and everyone else,
something cool's supposed
to happen if I capture you.
That sounds to me like you formed
some kind of alliance with Law.
Trusting him is an act of foolishness.
Take it from my own experience.
He will betray you.
Keep your advice!
I'll do whatever I wanna do!
You really are a glutton
for pain, aren't you?
Karakuni!
Oh, crap, I'm choking again.
Most people do that when
I remove their oxygen.
So this is the distance.
Yes, you've got me.
My powers are locked within a set radius.
The question is, how long can
you stay out of that radius?
Get ready for Gum-Gum!
I'm not giving you the jet!
Jet pistol!
That hurt, you dullard!
Although, it allowed me
to close the distance.
Not again.
That looks painful. Well, here.
Want your oxygen back?
Breathe in the blue sword.
Get ready to be slashed and seared.
Every gas is a weapon for me.
Maybe I can't kill you with poison,
but I've still got an entire arsenal
that'll put you in the ground.
I'm getting real tired of not breathing.
Quit running and give me your breath!
Quit chasing me!
Armament hardening!
This is it!
Gum-Gum, Jake Gottlieb!
Is that a wall?
Hey, what the hell? Igloo.
I'm impressed.
There aren't too many people alive that
could actually break through this wall.
You've got Devil Fruit powers?
It's time to go, Master.
this is a pointless fight you're
telling me so what you're just
gonna run do your worst Straw Hat
I've got bigger fish to fry but I'll
keep you in my thoughts when I use
your crew as test subjects for my
experiment enjoy your demise sorry
but you can't go after him I won't
let the master suffer any further
misfortune joker would kill me if
i allowed that you mean the pink
bird guy from the war what the hell
is up with that dude the gate's
closing we gotta run hooray ain't that
black-legged Sanji i don't get it
what's a Straw Hat doing helping us
Full power strike!
It don't look like Black
Lake's going to back down.
He's beating the hell
out of that fake Vergo.
We've got to give you some backup.
What are you morons doing?
Start running already.
They're trying to seal you
up in here to poison you.
What'd I tell you?
They're letting the gas in!
We better run for it!
Get a move on!
Well, look at that.
Now I get it.
You've got metal or something
under your skin, don't you?
Quit interfering.
This is an internal matter.
I'm familiar with your type.
My captain hates guys like you.
Oh, crap.
Hey, Blackley!
You're gonna run, man!
The main's closing!
You're gonna get trapped in there!
Turn around!
The gas is right behind you!
Get out of there!
This is an alert from Building D!
Attention all buildings in the
third laboratory! What now?
This is building D!
Attention all buildings
in the third laboratory!
The Warlord Shavulgar Law
has infiltrated the premises!
And he's just gained access
to the SAD Manufacturing Room!
Is he crazy?
What does that fool think he's doing?
If he goes through with this, he's gonna
bite off more than even he can chew!
So that's it.
That was his plan all along. What the?
You capture the Master
while he finds S .A .D.
Well, I finally see what
your little scheme is.
Law.
He formed an alliance with the
Strawhats just to keep us busy.
And he probably joined the Warlords
just so he can gain access to that room.
Crazy bastard.
He must have one seriously hellish
scenario banging around inside his skull.
Now, it's time to unleash
hell on the new world.
Whoa, hold on, don't close it yet.
Whoa, he's right, that fake
nirgle guy in Blackleg.
Haven't made it out yet.
It's too late.
The poison gas is about
to be all over the place.
There's nowhere to run.
They're dead.
Blackleg, no.
This isn't fair.
There's nothing we can do.
Hey.
Everyone made it.
You're looking good! It's him!
Especially you, sweetie!
You survived after all!
You really scared us, pal!
Keep on kicking ass, Blackwing!
Hey, you're awesome!
I don't care about you!
Gross!
I don't need a bunch of ugly
dudes singing my praise.
Ladies only!
Hey, you okay?
We can give you some
first aid if you got hurt.
Shut up!
Unless you can get me a kiss from
your captain, then I don't care!
I got lucky.
That guy could have destroyed me.
Who was that bastard anyway?
Some commander of yours or something?
What?
Not a chance!
Yeah, that was just someone
pretending to be the Vice Admiral!
He's a good guy!
You tell him what's up, Captain!
No, it can't be him.
Vice Admiral Vergo.
He thinks of the G5 as a sort of family.
He'd never do something like that.
Well, I've never met the guy myself,
so I couldn't tell you either way.
I just know that he turned
pale and ran off somewhere.
At any rate, we should get moving soon.
We're going to save those children
and get everyone out of this place.
Hey, whatever you say, we're all on board!
Law's going after S .A .D.
He is.
With this development, there's
no doubt he's betrayed us.
I see.
Well, I can't say I'm shocked.
But that's some gratitude
after I took him in.
I treated that punk like a
brother, and this is what I get?
A pity, huh?
Indeed it is.
He made it to the
manufacturing room, you said?
Here's what I'd do if I were him.
I'd destroy everything in sight.
Then I'd kidnap Caesar, I think.
Scratch that.
Maybe just kill him.
Bastard!
How could you do this to my love?
Get him out of the way and it's over.
He's the only one who can make S .A .D.
Or rather, he's the only
one who even knows how.
Frankly, if Law is able to pull that off,
Then we've got a big problem, Brook.
To be specific, it's a problem for
me, because this is my business.
If it dries up, people will be angry.
Hey, Baby Five, what the hell
do you think you're doing?
You're lucky the young
master's so forgiving.
I'm gonna kill him with my own two hands.
You can't stop me, damn it!
This is the last straw!
They say misfortune never comes alone. Oh.
Oh, so my misfortune is
going to be his next.
Poor Law, that adorable little scamp.
Young master, whatever are
you going to do to him?
You know darn well Law will
get exactly what he deserves.
That traitor.
I know this will be difficult for you,
Vergo, but I need you to take care of Law.
Also, make it as cruel and
gruesome as you can manage.
I want him to suffer.
I won't hold back.
In fact, Dolfi, I'll even take a
picture of this corpse for you.
How's that, son?
You remember my camera I'm always using?
That should do.
What the hell are you talking about?
You don't have a camera.
Oh, right.
Actually, I don't think I've ever
taken a single photo in my life.
How about I'll bring you an ear instead?
I like that idea even better.
Ba-da-ba-da-ba.
Aziza, Monet, can you hear me?
Joker, why, hello.
Oh, hello there.
You have to be careful with Law,
but Straw Hat's dangerous, too.
He acts stupid, but I've seen
him use the Conqueror's Haki.
He might have more potential than Law.
Baby Five here is armed to the
teeth and itching for a fight.
I'll send her along with Buffalo
to make certain things go smoothly.
When this is all over, come
back to Dressrosa immediately.
All right.
As you wish.
The dragon looks like a runt,
but it's actually causing a lot
more damage than the big one.
I like his attitude.
Get off my back and fight it!
You gotta go stop that thing!
It's turned this building
into a sea of flames.
this is bad isn't it those tanks
are on fire what happens if
one of them explodes then they
blow a giant hole in the wall
and all the poison gas from
outside pours in i don't care
how tough you are if that happens
every last one of us is dead
look no further my friend
see i have a score to
settle with dragon guy so
my fury shall be unbridled
by the might of this
sword i do swear the beast
shall be destroyed not so
fast that loathsome dragon
has done me a great wrong
and i will reclaim my
honor in blood and yet
did you notice its cruelty
he charged as if to consume
me then he turned away
as if i were some bag of
bones Dragons need meat,
I guess.
I'll have you know that
bones contain nutrients, too!
Yeah, I'll keep that in mind.
Kin'emon, please!
I insist that you let me
vanquish this dreadful dragon!
I'll take your revenge!
You stand back and watch me!
I'll do it myself!
You shall not!
I shall too! You shall not! I shall shall!
Uh, I mean...
Come on, come on!
Nin, nin, nin!
Are you casting a spell?
It's what samurai do!
It's ninja, actually.
Here goes.
Under trap!
What the cheating, Nami?
What a surprise!
Press Ben, girl, you're
proficient in the ninja arts.
Don't call me that, you weirdo!
Get a whiff of the
world's smelliest flower.
Now special attack,
Creepstar Rafflesia! Ah!
What?
The long-nosed goblin commits
frightful sorcery as well.
What did you call me?
Now for rent-up lure, Katorea Moon.
And ho!
Are you all-powerful ninja?
He's going down!
I'll be the one to finish him!
You shall do no such thing!
Follow my lead, Sir Corpse.
I will show you glory.
Foxfire style.
Flame split.
It cut fire again.
Splendid work. But of course.
Now for my cavat bon nevon.
And flaming flame.
Uh, did you just call me a corpse?
Uh, uh, well, that's fair enough.
Nice going!
Well, that's that.
So long, you great dummy!
Come on, say it!
Say the bones are delicious!
I'm waiting!
Beauty dragon, take that and another!
Curse you!
Is there a history between
you and dragons, Kin'emon?
Did one perhaps eat your family
or something of the sort?
Were that the case, my
grudge could be no greater!
I think we should go.
Get your bony bag back on
Brownie's tail or we'll leave you!
Please wait!
Hey, just in time, look up there!
That doesn't sound good.
He's in his monster form fighting the kid.
I can't even guess what's going on here.
All done, hmm.
Seems you're perfectly healthy.
You can go back to the biscuit room now.
You mean it?
Of course.
Get some candy.
Oh, yeah.
Where did that boy go?
He's not here anymore. Huh? The boy? Hmm.
I saw him go into the secret room
where we're not supposed to go.
And then something weird happened
and he turned into a dragon.
Momonosuke, you know?